wqxr.org 2011-12-09

# Privacy Policy - WQXR

### Online Privacy Policy

New York Public Radio (“NYPR”) values your participation in our public radio community, both online and offline, and assures you that your privacy is a priority to us. NYPR’s web sites adhere to a strict policy for ensuring the privacy of your personally identifiable information (such as full name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and/or other identifiable information) and preserving the integrity of this online medium.

### Visiting New York Public Radio’s Site

When you visit our sites, our web server automatically recognizes only your domain name, where you are coming to us from and what browser you are using. We use this information to analyze how traffic flows at our sites, but no one can contact or identify you from this information.

### Cookies

NYPR places an industry-standard "cookie" file on your computer to more accurately count the number of visitors and track activity on our websites. This cookie is totally anonymous and does not store any personal information about individual users. Cookies can also be used to store certain visitor preferences, like your favorite media player or a bulletin board password. In such cases, users have a choice of storing such information in a cookie or typing it each time they visit the site.

### E-mail Communications

NYPR regularly sends email Newsletters and membership correspondence to our registered members and visitors with information about NYPR programs, services or membership opportunities. If you do not wish to receive any email from NYPR, please indicate your preference on the pledge form when making a pledge, visit the e-mail newsletter sign up page to "opt-out", or contact Listener Services: [listenerservices@nypublicradio.org](mailto:listenerservices@nypublicradio.org) or (646) 829-4000. We will do our best to make your change in a timely manner.

NYPR never sells, exchanges or lends to third parties any email or telephone information you provide when making a Membership Pledge or subscribing to our E-mail communications.

### When You Make an Online Membership Pledge

NYPR will ask you to provide the information necessary to process and service your membership pledge: name, billing and shipping address, telephone number, email address, and credit card number. This information is encrypted for your security and is only seen by our membership staff who processes your gift and our contracted fulfillment agencies.

### List sharing policy

NYPR may occasionally share names and postal addresses collected through membership pledges with carefully selected organizations. If you do not want your address exchanged, please contact Listener Services: [listenerservices@nypublicradio.org](mailto:listenerservices@nypublicradio.org) or call (646) 829-4000 to classify your membership record as "No Exchange". It is NYPR policy not to sell or exchange e-mail addresses with any organization.

### Comments/Bulletin Board Participation

NYPR reserves the right to collect the e-mail addresses of those who post comments, messages to our bulletin board, information volunteered by the user, such as survey information and/or site registrations. The information we collect is to ensure compliance with bulletin board rules and occasionally to alert members and visitors to opt-in to our e-mail newsletter but is never shared with other organizations.

### Security

When you contribute to NYPR online, the information you provide is encrypted using a Secure Socket Layer Certificate (SSL) and transferred using secure protocol to NYPR where it is stored in a secure database. The SSL Certificate will provide 128-bit-encryption as long as users are running 128-bit enabled browsers. NYPR has aggressive security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

### Children: Under 13

You must be at least 13 years old in order to register for our Discussion Forums. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not send any information about yourself, including your name, address or e-mail address. If we discover that we have collected any personally-identifying information from a child under the age of 13, we will remove that information from our database as soon as possible.

### Age 13-18

Visitors between the ages of 13 and 18 must obtain permission from a parent or guardian before registering for the Discussions or otherwise sending any personally-identifying information.

Unless otherwise specified, you must be a least 18 years old in order to participate in any online contests.

**Links to other Sites and Services**

Please be advised that the NYPR’s site and services contain links to other sites, applications and services maintained by third parties that may not follow the same privacy policies as NYPR.  For instance, clicking or tapping on an underwriting notice or some third party logos will take you to an entirely different site, application or service. These sites, applications and services may use cookies, collect data, and use the data in ways that NYPR would not. NYPR is not responsible for the privacy practices or any information or materials on these other sites. Please visit these sites if you wish to review their privacy policies.

In some cases, the NYPR’s site and services may include certain embedded tools provided and controlled by third parties and governed by the terms and policies of the third parties. You should only use these third party tools if you agree to their respective terms and policies.

NYPR sites and services include a tool that allows you to sign in using information from your account with a third party service, such as Facebook, Twitter, Google, Yahoo, OpenID,  LinkedIn or other third party applications. Please be aware that those third party services are unrelated to NYPR, and that your use of the third party services is subject to the terms and policies of those services.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

NYPR will never use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice without notifying users. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our sites, attempt to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you have additional questions about how your personal information may be used or if you have questions or comments about our privacy policy, please contact us via e-mail at [listenerservices@nypublicradio.org](mailto:listenerservices@nypublicradio.org), by telephone at (646) 829-4000 or by mail at:

**Listener Services**  
New York Public Radio  
160 Varick Street  
New York, NY 10013
